[{"answer": "But it doesn't get more British than Sir David Frost.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "We're celebrating all those British institutions of the moment, aren't we?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "Well, I think it is partially because the royal family somehow -- I remember a time of Watergate and so on, some people said and friends of mine in the states said, god, I wish we had the same setup you had, where you have a head of state and a prime minister so that you can get rid of the prime minister without rocking the system.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "Why is it so important?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yes, because I mean when Nixon, who actually resigned, it was like the flag who was resigning in a way because the president -- even the discredited president, you know, has that aura about him which here you don't have with prime ministers and the rest.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "But as you just said, it can actually be quite useful to have an unelected body that has continuity that can control things when they go a little bit awry politically, isn't it?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "I mean Tony Blair, 13 year, I think?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "A royal duty in a way is slightly more inbred.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "How would you define duty as it affects a member of the royal family?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "And actually, it kind of encapsulates the reality of being a senior member of the royal family.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "And I thought, I'm stuck was a wonderfully modest way of describing becoming the king, you know?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "Well, I think the duty and so on would be an important thing.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "What do you think Diana would have make of his choice of bride and of the sense of duty that he's not accepting, really?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "I think he's -- he was always pretty deep, but I mean I think he's gotten much deeper.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "But how do you think Charles has matured from the day that you interviewed him as a teenager there?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "Do you think he gets an unfairly negative wrap, Prince Charles?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Well, when the president does it, that means that it is not illegal.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "So what in a sense you're saying is that there are certain situations, the Houston plan, or that part of it was one of them, where the president can decide that it's in the best interest of the nation or something and do something illegal?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "By definition?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "Poker face, poker face.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Your best poker face on?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Having seen the movie version of your interview, it's one of the best, I would say, movie accounts of a real story I've seen.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "And -- but I mean it was exhilarating inside that he'd gone that far because one knew that he'd never said it before, but that he damn well believed it, you know?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Well, we needed -- we needed $2 million basically.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "How much was it you (INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Well, I think it was a real landmark, certainly.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "I mean, of all the things you've done in your extraordinary career, was that -- does that remain the great high?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "A sense of -- a sense of euphoria or a joy, I guess.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "When he came out with those words?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "Well, there are odd lines with some people.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "Your other personal favorites, the moments you look back on and think, that was amazing?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "He's the greatest all around entertainer of all time.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Would you say that?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "As a present.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "We're going to have another short break.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "That's a great question.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "Of all the presidents, who was the most impressive?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "George H.W. Bush.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "If you could choose one to lead the country you were living in, which one would you choose?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "Well, that's going to be interesting, or President Sarah Palin.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "What do you think of the looming possibility of President Donald Trump?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "No, absolutely -- it's incredible why the Concord hasn't prevailed, because usually new discovers that work live on.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Not much progress, is it?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "Well, I nearly had an interview with Ariel Sharon.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Finally, who would you most like to interview in the world that you've never had the chance to interview?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Cyrus the Great because he was the first man ever to -- who used power to alleviate and improve the human condition and not make it worse.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Absolutely overwhelmed.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "What was it like?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "It's quite extraordinary, but on that particular day, I was on a flight to Moscow for the opening of a Reiss store.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Did you have a warning that she was going to wear one of your dresses?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "It's been absolutely extraordinary.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "Has business been crazy for that dress or similar dresses since Kate Middleton wore it?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "For the first few days, it was one a minute, literally.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "One a minute?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "What was that like for you?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "There's no question, she has a great sense of style.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "How do you think she's doing so far from the style perspective?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "I think she's still developing her style.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "What are you seeing so far?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "I've got to tell you, I was doing a press week in New York last week.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Could there be a moment where she steps out and we see you have a heart attack of excitement?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "Not at the moment, but --", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Do you do wedding dresses?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "This is the interesting thing.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "Will she be wearing one of her own dresses, do you think?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "I don't know if she's known for this type of clothing.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Two billion people watching, isn't she going to think, I'm going to wear one of my own?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Yes, I have, absolutely.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "You dressed David Beckham, haven't you?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "We're going to do something very traditional, a morning suit.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "What am I wearing?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "Just go full length.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "We'll only see you from here to here, right?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "The story today is that bets have been placed that the King George III tiara is the tiara that Kate will step out in.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Katie, what have you heard?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "It's very famous.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "First of all, it is pure speculation as to what she will be wearing on the day.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "What do you know right now?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "I don't know the exact numbers, but I would guess it's at least a dozen.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "How many tiaras does the queen have to either loan or give?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "Well, I think the fact that the queen wore it makes it extra special.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Why would it be, other than the fact that queens have wore them before?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "You guys actually repaired it, right?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "would be a great combination, yes.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "It would be kind of fitting if it was a Garrard jewel which was on top of her head, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "Let's go back to the priceless comment.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 671, "question": "For you guys, one of the top jewelers in the world, how important is it that someone like Kate Middleton wears your stuff?", "qSentId": 670}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110426pmt", "aSentId": 679, "question": "Are you excited?", "qSentId": 678}]